mark Manson the subtle art of not giving
a fuck a counterintuitive approach to
living a good life we live in an era of
opportunity whether we want to choose a
career a partner or a favorite news
source we have a multitude of options
available to us so why isn't it pure
bliss to be alive why are so many of a
stressed and unfulfilled we should have
everything we want we're so stressed out
because we're trying to do it all we
have so many options open to us we end
up concentrating on all our different
choices and opportunities all the time
so what can we do instead we need to
find out what is important to us and
concentrate on doing that everything
else well we shouldn't give a fuck about
it by limiting what we do we will be
happier and better people