By RentAnAdviser.com
What cha wanna be, when you grow up
What cha gonna do, when
your time is up
What cha gonna say, when
things go wrong
What cha wanna do, when
you're on your own
There's a road, long and winding
The lights are blindin',
but it gets there
Don't give up, don't look back
There's a silver linin', it's
out there somewhere
Everybody wants an answer,
everybody needs a friend
We all need a shinin' star
on which we can depend
N' so tonight we're gonna
wish upon a star
We never wished upon before (to
find what you're looking for)
There'll be times, in your life
Ya when you' be dancin' n' shit,
but you ain't gettin it
But don't get disillusioned,
no, don't expect too much
'Cause if what you have is all
you can get just keep on
Tryin', it just ain't happened yet
Everybody wants to be winner,
everybody has a dream
We all need a shinin' star when
things ain't what they seem
So tonight we're gonna
wish upon a star
We never wished upon before (gotta
get where you're headed for)
Everybody wants some kindness,
everybody needs a break
We all need a shinin' star when
things get hard to take
So tonight we're gonna
wish upon a star
We never wished upon before
So tonight we're gonna
wish upon a star
We never wished upon before
By RentAnAdviser.com